usadsciti.com 2015-12-06

# Classifieds, Free Classifieds, Online Classifieds, Free Ads | US Ads Citi

##  Website Privacy Policy 

[UsAdsCiti.com](http://www.usadsciti.com/) values the privacy of information pertaining to its associates. We do not sell or use any information obtained from our site in an unethical manner. Any information obtained such as Usernames, IP addresses, email, etc are only used in the administration of our website and services. We may email our members about site related issues, events, etc. Only in the case of illegal activity, harassment, or other questionable activities would your information be shared with a third party. We may also release data under warrant from law enforcement and related authorities.

By your use of the UsAdsCiti.com website, you expressly consent to our disclosure and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies.  
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and we will post any new versions on this page.

We will enable you to communicate your privacy concerns to us and that we will respond to them appropriately. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at [support@UsAdsCiti.com](mailto:support@UsAdsCiti.com)

Thank you for choosing [UsAdsCiti.com](http://www.usadsciti.com/) and we hope you enjoy this free service.
